<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
    <dublin_core schema="dc">
    <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Jaafar, Nurjanah Mohd</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Ainsworth, Shaaron</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">van Heuven, Walter</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="accessioned">2018-11-04T23:26:23Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="available">2018-11-04T23:26:23Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="issued">2018-07</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="citation" language="en_US">Jaafar, N. M., Ainsworth, S., &amp; van Heuven, W.&#x20;(2018).&#x20;Learning With Multi-representational Texts in a Second Language. An Eye-tracking Investigation.&#x20;In&#x20;Kay,&#x20;J.&#x20;and&#x20;Luckin,&#x20;R.&#x20;(Eds.) Rethinking Learning in the Digital Age: Making the Learning Sciences Count, 13th International Conference of the Learning Sciences (ICLS) 2018, Volume 2. London, UK: International Society of the Learning Sciences.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="uri">https://doi.dx.org&#x2F;10.22318&#x2F;cscl2018.969</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="abstract" language="en_US">Integrating verbal and pictorial information is fundamental to learning multi-representational materials and it is often reported to positively correlate with learning outcomes. This however may only be applicable to those learning the materials in their native language as little research has been conducted with the non-native speakers. To address this issue, we investigated the reading of a multi-representational English text with 32 second language English speakers and its relationship with second language proficiency and learning outcomes. Using eye-tracking, we found that readers could be divided into two groups based on the extent they integrated texts and pictures. The difference in the amount of integration in the two groups could not be explained by English proficiency nor by prior knowledge. The groups also performed differently in the post-test with high integrators performing better, hence demonstrating that text-picture integration is equally important when reading multi-representational texts in the second language. </dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="iso" language="en_US">en</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en_US"> International&#x20;Society&#x20;of&#x20;the&#x20;Learning&#x20;Sciences,&#x20;Inc.&#x20;[ISLS].</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Learning With Multi-representational Texts in a Second Language. An Eye-tracking Investigation</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="type" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Book&#x20;chapter</dcvalue>
      <dc:subject xml:lang="en">Multi-representational learning</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">text-picture integration</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">eye movements</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">reading in a second language</dc:subject>
    </dublin_core>