<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
    <dublin_core schema="dc">
    <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Settlage, John</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="accessioned">2018-11-04T23:35:54Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="available">2018-11-04T23:35:54Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="issued">2018-07</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="citation" language="en_US">Settlage, J.&#x20;(2018).&#x20;Equitable Science Outcomes and School Organizational Conditions.&#x20;In&#x20;Kay,&#x20;J.&#x20;and&#x20;Luckin,&#x20;R.&#x20;(Eds.) Rethinking Learning in the Digital Age: Making the Learning Sciences Count, 13th International Conference of the Learning Sciences (ICLS) 2018, Volume 3. London, UK: International Society of the Learning Sciences.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="uri">https://doi.dx.org&#x2F;10.22318&#x2F;cscl2018.1345</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="abstract" language="en_US">Achievement gap severity is not a matter of uneven resource distribution between towns or districts. Rather, schools with comparable demographic profiles generate widely varied results. Inequities correspond to conditions inside schools. This predicament suggests that learning research would benefit by drawing upon sociological frameworks. Individual students are embedded within peer groups, classrooms are constituted by multiple inter-relationships, and school level learning is shaped by complex interactions amongst adults and children. My research has revealed multiple institutional factors strongly associated with student outcomes and those suggest that equity agendas should more intentionally attend to organizational factors.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="iso" language="en_US">en</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en_US"> International&#x20;Society&#x20;of&#x20;the&#x20;Learning&#x20;Sciences,&#x20;Inc.&#x20;[ISLS].</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Equitable Science Outcomes and School Organizational Conditions</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="type" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Book&#x20;chapter</dcvalue>
      <dc:subject xml:lang="en">educational inequities</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">achievement disparities</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">organizational factors</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">science outcomes</dc:subject>
    </dublin_core>