<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
    <dublin_core schema="dc">
    <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Wang, Yu-Chi</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Doll, Jenifer</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Varma, Keisha</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="accessioned">2018-11-04T23:26:23Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="available">2018-11-04T23:26:23Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="issued">2018-07</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="citation" language="en_US">Wang, Y., Doll, J., &amp; Varma, K.&#x20;(2018).&#x20;"Your Turn!”: Playing Cooperative Modern Board Games to Promote Perspective Taking and Cooperative Attitudes.&#x20;In&#x20;Kay,&#x20;J.&#x20;and&#x20;Luckin,&#x20;R.&#x20;(Eds.) Rethinking Learning in the Digital Age: Making the Learning Sciences Count, 13th International Conference of the Learning Sciences (ICLS) 2018, Volume 2. London, UK: International Society of the Learning Sciences.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="uri">https://doi.dx.org&#x2F;10.22318&#x2F;cscl2018.913</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="abstract" language="en_US">Though social and emotional learning (SEL) interventions successfully foster enhanced social, emotional, and academic outcomes, the research on engaging methods for teaching specific skills has been limited.  This study investigates the potential for modern board games to foster SEL competencies through Cooperative Learning Theory. Because cooperative modern board games combine motivating gameplay and designs that align with elements from Cooperative Learning Theory, they may enhance cooperative attitudes and perspective taking skills.  In this pre-test/post-test quasi-experiment, middle school students played either a cooperative or competitive board game.  Students who played and highly enjoyed the cooperative game showed significantly greater increases in perspective taking skills after gameplay (F=11.42, p=.001), suggesting that playing enjoyable cooperative modern board games may be associated with increased perspective taking skills.  Our findings suggest the need for further investigation into board games as a low-cost platform for students to practice SEL skills outside of the formal classroom environment.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="iso" language="en_US">en</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en_US"> International&#x20;Society&#x20;of&#x20;the&#x20;Learning&#x20;Sciences,&#x20;Inc.&#x20;[ISLS].</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en_US">"Your Turn!”: Playing Cooperative Modern Board Games to Promote Perspective Taking and Cooperative Attitudes</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="type" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Book&#x20;chapter</dcvalue>
      <dc:subject xml:lang="en">Cooperative Learning</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">Social and Emotional Learning</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">Board Games</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">Games</dc:subject>
    </dublin_core>