<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
    <dublin_core schema="dc">
    <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Yang, Hui</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Mouza, Chrystalla</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Pan, Yi-Cheng</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="accessioned">2018-11-04T23:14:21Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="available">2018-11-04T23:14:21Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="issued">2018-07</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="citation" language="en_US">Yang, H., Mouza, C., &amp; Pan, Y.&#x20;(2018).&#x20;Examining Pre-service Teacher Knowledge Trajectories of Computational Thinking through a Redesigned Educational Technology Course .&#x20;In&#x20;Kay,&#x20;J.&#x20;and&#x20;Luckin,&#x20;R.&#x20;(Eds.) Rethinking Learning in the Digital Age: Making the Learning Sciences Count, 13th International Conference of the Learning Sciences (ICLS) 2018, Volume 1. London, UK: International Society of the Learning Sciences.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="uri">https://doi.dx.org&#x2F;10.22318&#x2F;cscl2018.368</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="abstract" language="en_US">Computation Thinking (CT) is a fundamental skill of analytical thinking. To successfully infuse CT into K-8 settings, we must equip pre-service teachers with CT knowledge and skills that can be applied in their curricular context. This work presents trajectories of pre-service teacher knowledge development of CT concepts and computing tools within the context of disciplinary content and pedagogical knowledge through their participation in an educational technology course. Data were collected from a random sample of 42 pre-service teachers. Data sources included participants’ lesson plans (N=126) collected through three different time points. These materials were analyzed quantitatively and qualitatively. Preliminary results indicated that pre-service teachers gradually improved their understanding throughout their participation in the course. Findings also revealed difficulties in conceptualizing and integrating CT in conjunction with content and pedagogy, particularly during authentic vis-à-vis hypothetical lesson designs.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="iso" language="en_US">en</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en_US"> International&#x20;Society&#x20;of&#x20;the&#x20;Learning&#x20;Sciences,&#x20;Inc.&#x20;[ISLS].</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Examining Pre-service Teacher Knowledge Trajectories of Computational Thinking through a Redesigned Educational Technology Course </dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="type" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Book&#x20;chapter</dcvalue>
      <dc:subject xml:lang="en">Teacher knowledge</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">teacher education</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">computational thinking</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">mixed-methods</dc:subject>
    </dublin_core>