<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
    <dublin_core schema="dc">
    <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Xie, Bin</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Reilly, Joseph M</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Dich, Yong Li</dcvalue>
<dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author">Schneider, Bertrand</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="accessioned">2018-11-04T23:14:21Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="available">2018-11-04T23:14:21Z</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="issued">2018-07</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="citation" language="en_US">Xie, B., Reilly, J. M., Dich, Y. L., &amp; Schneider, B.&#x20;(2018).&#x20;Augmenting Qualitative Analyses of Collaborative Learning Groups Through Multi-Modal Sensing .&#x20;In&#x20;Kay,&#x20;J.&#x20;and&#x20;Luckin,&#x20;R.&#x20;(Eds.) Rethinking Learning in the Digital Age: Making the Learning Sciences Count, 13th International Conference of the Learning Sciences (ICLS) 2018, Volume 1. London, UK: International Society of the Learning Sciences.</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="uri">https://doi.dx.org&#x2F;10.22318&#x2F;cscl2018.608</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="abstract" language="en_US">In a previous study (N=84), we collected information about dyads who worked on an engineering task typical of makerspaces: programming a robot to solve mazes of increasing difficulty. We collected multimodal data using a variety of sensors, including mobile eye-trackers, galvanic skin response, motion sensors and audio / video streams. In this paper, we contrast two pairs that exhibited positive and negative learning gains. We first detail multimodal measures to compare differences and similarities across those groups, and then dive deeper into a qualitative analysis of their exchanges. We then describe how those measures could be used over the entire sample to capture productive interactions in small groups. We conclude by discussing how process data from sensors can augment traditional qualitative observations, and how it can create powerful synergies for better understanding collaborative interactions among learners in settings such as makerspaces. </dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="iso" language="en_US">en</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en_US"> International&#x20;Society&#x20;of&#x20;the&#x20;Learning&#x20;Sciences,&#x20;Inc.&#x20;[ISLS].</dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Augmenting Qualitative Analyses of Collaborative Learning Groups Through Multi-Modal Sensing </dcvalue>
      <dcvalue element="type" qualifier="none" language="en_US">Book&#x20;chapter</dcvalue>
      <dc:subject xml:lang="en">Multimodal Learning Analytics</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">Collaborative Learning</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">Makerspaces</dc:subject>
<dc:subject xml:lang="en">STEM learning</dc:subject>
    </dublin_core>